Now we're going to talk about The Grapevine.
The Grapevine is a traveling step.
You can use it to travel side to side, or you can use it to travel diagonally forward, or diagonally back.
So, starting with your right foot, you're going to step to the side.
Then you're going to cross back.
Then you're going to open out to the side, and then you're going to cross front.
Then you're going to open out to the side, cross back, and repeat.
Step out, cross back, step out, cross front.
Now we're going to try The Grapevine a little bit faster.
Out, back, out, front.
If you wanted to do The Grapevine in place, you can also do right to left, so you can step to the side, cross back, side, cross front; step side, cross back, side, cross front; side, cross back, side, cross front; side, cross back, side, cross front.